[
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "TYPE_ALIAS",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a type alias called ImageEncoding16?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "TYPE_ALIAS",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the definition of type alias ImageEncoding16?",
    "answer": "Enum[RGB16, RGBA16, BGR16, BGRA16, MONO16, 16UC1, 16UC2, 16UC3, 16UC4, \n        16SC1, 16SC2, 16SC3, 16SC4, BAYER_RGGB16, BAYER_BGGR16, BAYER_GBRG16, BAYER_GRBG16]"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "TYPE_ALIAS",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a type alias called ImageEncoding32?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "TYPE_ALIAS",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the definition of type alias ImageEncoding32?",
    "answer": "Enum[32SC1, 32SC2, 32SC3, 32SC4, 32FC1, 32FC2, 32FC3, 32FC4]"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "TYPE_ALIAS",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a type alias called Meter?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "TYPE_ALIAS",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the definition of type alias Meter?",
    "answer": "int8"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "TYPE_ALIAS",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a type alias called Millimeter?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "TYPE_ALIAS",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the definition of type alias Millimeter?",
    "answer": "int8"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "MESSAGE_ALIAS",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a message alias called ImageWith16Encoding?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "MESSAGE_ALIAS",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the base message type of message alias ImageWith16Encoding?",
    "answer": "sensor_msgs/Image"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "MESSAGE_FIELD",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "Which fields are defined in message alias ImageWith16Encoding?",
    "answer": "data, encoding, header"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "MESSAGE_FIELD",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the type of field header in message alias ImageWith16Encoding?",
    "answer": "Header"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "MESSAGE_FIELD",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the type of field encoding in message alias ImageWith16Encoding?",
    "answer": "ImageEncoding16"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "MESSAGE_FIELD",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the type of field data in message alias ImageWith16Encoding?",
    "answer": "Millimeter[]"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "MESSAGE_ALIAS",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a message alias called ImageWith32Encoding?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "MESSAGE_ALIAS",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the base message type of message alias ImageWith32Encoding?",
    "answer": "sensor_msgs/Image"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "MESSAGE_FIELD",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "Which fields are defined in message alias ImageWith32Encoding?",
    "answer": "data, encoding, header"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "MESSAGE_FIELD",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the type of field header in message alias ImageWith32Encoding?",
    "answer": "Header"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "MESSAGE_FIELD",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the type of field encoding in message alias ImageWith32Encoding?",
    "answer": "ImageEncoding32"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "MESSAGE_FIELD",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the type of field data in message alias ImageWith32Encoding?",
    "answer": "Meter[]"
  }
]